reservebar.com 2019-06-11

# Privacy Policy | Buy Online or Send as a Gift | ReserveBar

ReserveBar knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. This privacy policy lets you know what information we collect, how we may from time to time share that information, and your choices regarding the sharing of your information.

**How To Contact Us**  
If you have questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us in the following ways: 

Phone: 1-855-588-1277

Email:  [info@reservebar.com](mailto:info@reservebar.com)

## Privacy Policy Contents

  * Our Privacy Commitment to Our Customers
  * Acceptance of and Changes to this Privacy Statement
  * Information Collection and Use
  * Cookies & Clickstream Technology
  * Updating Your Personal Information
  * Account Registration
  * Security of Your Personal Information
  * Disclosure of Personal Information
  * Information from Third Parties
  * Children’s and Minor’s Privacy
  * California Privacy Rights

## OUR PRIVACY COMMITMENT TO OUR CUSTOMERS

We value the relationship we have with our customers and are committed to responsible information-handling practices. We take great care in safeguarding your personal information and in complying with all applicable federal and state privacy laws and our own internal standards and best practices.

We follow these privacy principles in connection with the collection, use, security and sharing of customer information:

  * **CHOICE.**  When we contact you for marketing purposes, we will let you know how to remove your name from future marketing efforts.
  * **SECURITY.**  We will use reasonable security measures to protect the personal information we receive from you. 

## ACCEPTANCE OF AND CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT

As ReserveBar continues to improve the services, products and the features we provide via the ReserveBar.com website, our privacy policy is subject to change. **Please note that we may amend this policy at any time by posting the amended policy in this Privacy Policy section of the ReserveBar.com website.**

**By using the ReserveBar.com website and services, you signify and confirm your acceptance of this Privacy Statement. If you do not agree or are not comfortable with any policy described in this Privacy Statement, your only remedy is to discontinue use of the ReserveBar.com website. We expressly reserve the right to modify this Privacy Statement at any time.** **Your continued use of any portion of the ReserveBar.com website following notification or posting of such changes, will constitute your acceptance of those changes.** If you have questions or concerns about our specific policies, please send an e-mail to [info@reservebar.com](mailto:info@reservebar.com). 

## INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE

ReserveBar is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We collect, use and disclose your Personal Information (including individuals associated with you, all of whom are referred to as “you” in this Privacy Policy) in its normal course of business for the following purposes:

  * Providing you with products and services offered on our site which you are interested in;
  * To determine your location so we know we can target certain offer certain products to you;
  * Establishing and maintaining communications with you;
  * Where you have requested information from us or one of our partners, assisting in the response to your request for information;
  * Responding to your inquiries about purchases, accounts and other services;
  * Marketing our, and our affiliates and partner’s, goods and services to you;
  * Processing transactions through service providers;
  * Meeting legal, security, processing and regulatory requirements;
  * Protecting against fraud, suspicious or other illegal activities; and
  * Compiling statistics for analysis of our sites and our business.

We will not sell, share or rent this information to others in any way that varies from what is disclosed in this statement. ReserveBar collects information from our users at several different areas on our site. You may receive information regarding new features, services and special offers we think you will find valuable. If you wish to access, update or delete the information that you have previously provided to us and are unable to do so via the site, please contact us by e-mail at [info@reservebar.com](mailto:info@reservebar.com). 

## COOKIES & CLICKSTREAM TECHNOLOGY

As you navigate the site, we may also collect information through the use of commonly-used information-gathering tools, such as cookies and web beacons (collectively “Website Navigational Information”). Website Navigational Information includes standard information from your web browser (such as browser type and browser language), your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, and the actions you take on the Site (such as the web pages viewed and the links clicked).

_Cookies_

Like many companies, we may use cookies on this Site. Cookies are pieces of information shared between your web browser and a website. Use of cookies enables a faster and easier experience for the user. A cookie cannot read data off your computer's hard drive.

There are different kinds of cookies with different functions:

(i) Session cookies: these are only stored on your computer during your web session. They are automatically deleted when the browser is closed. They usually store an anonymous session ID allowing you to browse a website without having to log in to each page. They do not collect any information from your computer.

(ii) Persistent cookies: a persistent cookie is one stored as a file on your computer, and it remains there when you close your web browser. The cookie can be read by the website that created it when you visit that website again.

(iii) First-party cookies: the function of this type of cookie is to retain your preferences for a particular website for the entity that owns that website. They are stored and sent between ReserveBar’s servers and your computer’s hard drive. They are not used for anything other than for personalization as set by you. These cookies may be either Session or Persistent cookies.

(iv) Third-party cookies: the function of this type of cookie is to retain your interaction with a particular website for an entity that does not own that website. They are stored and sent between the Third-party’s server and your computer’s hard drive. These cookies are usually Persistent cookies.

We do use third-party cookies on our Sites, as well as third party provided web beacons (please see the section on Web Beacons below). These cookies are used by us and our marketing partners to better understand your preferences, purchases and/or to tailor your experience on the site to your interests.

More specifically, this Site uses Google Analytics and other similar services, which are web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. and other third party companies. These services use cookies to help the website analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by these vendors on servers in the United States. These vendors will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity, and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage for ReserveBar and its marketing affiliates. These vendors may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on their behalf. These vendors will not associate your IP address with any other data held by them. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. **By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google and ReserveBar in the manner and for the purposes set out above.**

Along with the above noted uses, we use cookies for the following purposes:

_Where strictly necessary_

These cookies are essential in order to enable you to move around the Site and use its features, such as accessing secure areas of the Site. Without these cookies, services you have asked for, such as obtaining a quote or logging into your account, cannot be provided. These cookies do not gather information about you that could be used for marketing or remembering where you have been on the internet.

_Performance_

These cookies collect information about how visitors use a Site, for instance which pages visitors go to most often, and if they get error messages from web pages. They also allow us to record and count the number of visitors to the Site, all of which enables us to see how visitors use the Site in order to improve the way that our Site works. These cookies do not collect information that identifies a person, as all information these cookies collect is anonymous and is used to improve how our Site works.

_Functionality_

These cookies allow our Site to remember choices you make (such as your user name, language or the region you are in) and provide enhanced features. For instance, the Site needs to remember your log in details, so that you do not have to repeatedly sign in to your account when using a particular device to access our Site. These cookies can also be used to remember changes you have made to text size, font and other parts of web pages that you may be able to customize from time to time. They may also be used to provide services you have requested such as viewing a video or commenting on an article. The information these cookies collect is usually anonymized. They do not gather any information about you that could be used for advertising or remember where you have been on the internet.

For information on all of these categories of cookies, and for more information generally on cookies please refer to [aboutcookies.org](http://aboutcookies.org/). Please consult your web browser's ‘Help’ documentation or visit [aboutcookies.org](http://aboutcookies.org/). for more information about how to turn cookies on and off for your browser.

_Web Beacons_

The Site may also use web beacons (including web beacons supplied or provided by third parties) alone or in conjunction with cookies to compile information about users’ usage of the Site and interaction with e-mails from ReserveBar. Web beacons are clear electronic images that can recognize certain types of information on your computer, such as cookies, when you viewed a particular Site tied to the web beacon, and a description of a Site tied to the web beacon. We use web beacons to operate and improve the Sites and e-mail communications. We may use information from web beacons in combination with other data we have about our clients to provide you with information about ReserveBar and our services. We will conduct this review on an anonymous basis.

_IP Addresses_

When you visit our Sites, ReserveBar collects your Internet Protocol (“IP”) addresses to track and aggregate non-Personal Information. For example, ReserveBar uses IP addresses to monitor the regions from which users navigate the Sites. IP addresses will be stored in such a way so that you cannot be identified from the IP address. In addition, ReserveBar uses yor IP address to get an approximate location so we can find offer you targeted marketing or other services based on your location. We do this for both your convenience, as well as for legal compliance reasons.

_Do-Not-Track_

The major browsers have attempted to implement the draft “Do Not Track” (“DNT”) standard of the World Wide Web Consortium (“W3C”) in their latest releases. As this standard has not been finalized, the ReserveBar site is not compatible with DNT.

## UPDATING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

ReserveBar wants your personal information to be accurate and complete. We provide different methods for you to update your personal information. To update your name, address, phone number and/or e-mail information, please contact us as follows: 

PHONE: 1-855-588-1277

E-MAIL: [info@reservebar.com](mailto:info@reservebar.com)

MAIL: ReserveBar

426 Main Street

Ridgefield, CT 06877

Attention: Customer Service

If you send an e-mail or letter request, please be sure to include your current information and the requested changes.

## E-MAIL & ACCOUNT REGISTRATION

During registration on the Web site, we collect an e-mail address to communicate with you about your transaction. We use this e-mail address to contact you if there are any issues and to notify you about the status of your order. If you do not want this retained for future promotional e-mail inclusion, you may opt-out any time by contacting us.

If a user wishes to subscribe to our e-mails, we ask for contact information such as name and e-mail address. We may use your personal information for purposes of sending you promotional materials and for other reason. For example, we may use your information to send you administrative communications about any account you may have with us or about future changes to this Privacy Policy. If at any time you should wish to unsubscribe, please click on the “unsubscribe” link in any e-mail from us or send an e-mail to info@reservebar.com.

When you register as a member of the ReserveBar website or sign up to receive our e-mail offers, we collect information that helps us identify you. The more information you provide, the better we can customize our services and your experience to suit your needs and preferences.

## SECURITY OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

Whether you are shopping online, we use reasonable security measures to protect the confidentiality of personal information under our control and appropriately limit access to it. **ReserveBar cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us by e-mail, and you do so at your own risk.**

The ReserveBar website uses Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption technology provided by VeriSign, a premier encryption software company, to protect your personal information during data transport, including your name, address and credit card number. On a secure page such as our order form, the lock icon on your Web browser switches to locked, as opposed to unlocked mode, and back to open mode when you are just browsing.

When you create an account on ReserveBar.com you are required to establish a password. To maximize your level of protection, you should choose at least 6-20 characters, using a combination of both letters and numbers. You are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your password and account information. You have the ability to purchase on our site without creating an account; however, you will need to reenter your personal information each time you use our site in order to make a purchase.

## DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

We do not disclose any Personal Information about you to any third parties except as stated in this Privacy Policy, as otherwise permitted by law, or authorized by you.

Purchasing

Third parties to whom we disclose information are required by law and contractual undertakings to keep your Personal Information confidential and secure, and to use and disclose it for purposes that a reasonable person would consider appropriate in the circumstances, in compliance with all applicable legislation, which purposes are as follows:

  * To partners who offer products or services via our site so they can transact with you;
  * To notify you or allow our affiliated companies to notify you of certain products or services offered by our affiliated companies;
  * For legal, claims settlement and valuation services;
  * To process transactions through data processing service providers;
  * If the information is a credit card number and related information, to process credit card payments—through third party payment processing, clearing and settlement systems in association with various banks; and

If these third parties wish to use your Personal Information for any other purpose, they will have a legal obligation to notify you of this and, where required, to obtain your consent. Contact us at info@reservebar.com for more information on these third parties.

_Co-Branded Areas_

Some areas in our site may be offered to you in association with affiliated third parties, such as co-promotional partners, dedicated producers of beverage alcohol, or co-sponsors of events you may want to attend. Such co-branded areas may require you to disclose Personal Information to the third party. The co-branded areas will identify the third party. The third party’s privacy policy will apply to how they treat your Personal Information. We recommend you review the privacy policy of these third parties. If you elect to register for events or products with these third parties you will be providing your Personal Information to both us, and the third party.

_Service Providers_

We use third-party service providers to enhance your shopping experience on our Web site including, but not limited to, providing shipping services, tax services and product recommendations. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, e-mail address or telephone number) about your visits to this Web site in order to provide personalized recommendations and advertisements about our goods and services on our Web site as well as when you visit other Web sites. Because service providers we use may be located in the United States, your Personal Information may be processed and stored inside the United States; and the U.S. government, courts, or law enforcement or regulatory agencies may be able to obtain disclosure of your Personal Information under US laws.

_Social Media, Reviews, and User Generated Content_

Any personally identifiable information you submit on a social media Web site, such as Facebook or Twitter, bulletin board, blog, chat room, comment about a product, or any other public forum on this Web site can be read, collected or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We recommend that you do not provide your name, e-mail address or any other personal information in public forums on this Site. Please note that if you choose to do so, it is at your own risk and you accept full responsibility for those posts and any consequences that may arise from posting this information.

_Business Transactions_

As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy assets. In such transactions, user information, including Personal Information, generally is one of the transferred business assets. Also, if either ReserveBar itself or substantially all of ReserveBar assets were acquired, your Personal Information may be one of the transferred assets. Therefore, we may disclose and/or transfer your Personal Information to a third party purchaser in these circumstances

_Other Legally Required Disclosures_

ReserveBar preserves the right to disclose without your prior permission any Personal Information about you or your use of this Site if ReserveBar has a good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) protect and defend the rights, property or safety of ReserveBar, employees, other users of this Site, or the public; (b) enforce the terms and conditions that apply to use of this Site; (c) as required by a legally valid request from a competent governmental authority; or (d) respond to claims that any content violates the rights of third-parties. We may also disclose Personal Information as we deem necessary to satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request

In this Privacy Policy, the purposes identified above and in “Collection, Use and Disclosure of Personal Information” will be referred to as the “Identified Purposes.”

## INFORMATION FROM THIRD PARTIES

ReserveBar obtains consumer information from third party providers in order to improve the accuracy of our customer database, increase our understanding of our customers or to identify potential customers. For example, we may get updated addresses from the National Change of Address (NCOA) service to ensure we have the correct contact information for our customers.

The third parties with whom we conduct business are authorized to use your information only to perform the service for which they are hired. They are required to abide by the terms of our Privacy Policy including taking reasonable measures to ensure your personal information is secure. We may also share aggregated data with third parties for analysis and research purposes. This data does not contain name, address or other personally identifiable information.

## CHILDREN’S AND MINOR’S PRIVACY

The ReserveBar.com site is intended for adults 21 years of age and older. We do not knowingly collect personal information from minors under the age of 21. However, if the parent or guardian of a child or minor under 21 believes that the child or minor has provided us with personally identifiable information, the parent or guardian of that child should contact us immediately at [info@reservebar.com](mailto:info@reservebar.com) if they want this information deleted from our files. 

## CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS

Pursuant to Section 1798.83 of the California Civil Code, residents of California have the right to request from a business, with whom the California resident has an established business relationship, certain information with respect to the types of personal information the business shares with third parties for direct marketing purposes by such third party and the identities of the third parties with whom the business has shared such information during the immediately preceding calendar year.

To request a copy of the information disclosure provided by ReserveBar pursuant to Section 1798.83 of the California Civil Code, please contact [info@reservebar.com](mailto:info@reservebar.com).

Use left/right arrows to navigate the slideshow or swipe left/right if using a mobile device
